is a lot less secure than we all seem to
assume it is but very few people
actually know that and we sort of feel
like uh those people that are you know
in front of the board with all the
string attached being like crazy like
it's vulnerable and it's like nobody
cares uh out there because their
business is continuing to operate and
they're like why would I pay you know
millions of dollars in in uh running a
security program when I continue to
operate just fine and you know I have no
service outages and I make all this
Revenue like whatever right million fine
doesn't cost Millions it doesn't cost
Millions to run a bug Bounty program
most most only pay a couple hundred
thousand and if uh I promise uh if uh if
your bug Bounty program Burns $50,000 in
the first two months you got bigger
problems sure and that's exactly it is
the you got biger problem is usually
where you are yeah yeah put a little
money in your bug bount program and if
it disappears fast uh oh that's well go
go make other Investments right go make
other Investments